<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Misc on Scott Westover</title>
    <link>https://scottwestover.github.io/tags/misc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Misc on Scott Westover</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 01:24:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://scottwestover.github.io/tags/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Updates</title>
      <link>https://scottwestover.github.io/post/2018/07/under-contruction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 01:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scottwestover.github.io/post/2018/07/under-contruction/</guid>
      <description>After working with the Hugo static site generator, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided that I wanted to move my blog over to this template.
For the most part, this should be an easy transition since all of the blog files were already Markdown files, but with the transition, there could be some small issues.
Hopefully this will be a smooth transition, and I hope you like the new site design!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Web App</title>
      <link>https://scottwestover.github.io/post/2018/02/progressive-web-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 02:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scottwestover.github.io/post/2018/02/progressive-web-app/</guid>
      <description>At the beginning of January, I was accepted into the Grow With Google Scholarship from Udacity. If you are not familar with this program, I really recommend that you check it out. Basically, Google is scholarships for the Nano degrees that are available on Udacity. However, the scholarship is split into two phases.
During the first phase, they admit 10,000 or 15,000 into the first phase (depends on which track you applied for), and you have 3 months to complete the courses that they make available to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching to Hexo</title>
      <link>https://scottwestover.github.io/post/2018/02/switching-to-hexo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 23:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://scottwestover.github.io/post/2018/02/switching-to-hexo/</guid>
      <description>Update: 2018-07-15 - With the new updates to the blog it is no longer a PWA. This is coming soon&amp;hellip;
It has been awhile since my last post, and with a new year, I figured it was time for a change. I started looking into new ways to blog, and I decided to give Hexo a try.
Also, with the switch to a new platform, I decided to update the look of my blog and went with a simple theme so I could just focus on the blog posts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>